this tutorial is about how to use
本教程是关于如何使用的
不对称v形折叠以提高结构
this tutorial is about how to use
asymmetric v-folds to raise a structure
在页面的第一侧
我得到的例子是马修的妈妈
asymmetric v-folds to raise a structure
on one side of the page the first
赖因哈特
由莫里斯·森达克（Maurice Sendak）和
on one side of the page the first
example I've got is mommy by Matthew
最后的惊人的传播在你右边
得到了这瓣，这是结构
example I've got is mommy by Matthew
Reinhart
雕塑正在做这是沟
在这里，这是雕塑
Reinhart
illustrated by Maurice Sendak and the
在它的一侧被抬起，这些
这里有两个小块
illustrated by Maurice Sendak and the
final amazing spread on the right you've
不对称的v形褶皱可提升整体
事情真的很令人愉快
final amazing spread on the right you've
got this flap this is the structure the
头部移动手臂的方式
我可以告诉你以前的哪个
got this flap this is the structure the
sculpture being made this is the gully
教程通向本教程
是非对称v形折叠教程5是
sculpture being made this is the gully
down here and this is the sculpture
内置的平行四边形
教程15是动人的手臂和教程
down here and this is the sculpture
being raised on one side of it and these
24是圆周运动，所以这些都是
曾经使那个机制和
being raised on one side of it and these
two little pieces here these are the
我想告诉你的另一个是这个
一个非常不同的
two little pieces here these are the
asymmetric v-folds that lift the whole
这是弹出书和童谣
再次是Mathew Reinhardt讲的
asymmetric v-folds that lift the whole
thing really delightful piece of work
价差，在这种情况下，这是
一个提出的结构
thing really delightful piece of work
that the way the head moves the arms
折痕的一面
不对称的V吊舱实际上是隐藏的
that the way the head moves the arms
move I can tell you which previous
在这个浮动飞机下面，所以在这里
你可以看到这是水上飞机
move I can tell you which previous
tutorials lead up to this tutorial for
这是不对称的V折
被用来提高这种结构，如果你
tutorials lead up to this tutorial for
is asymmetric v-folds tutorial 5 is
看一下这个结构就可以了
看到所有的平行四边形都在
is asymmetric v-folds tutorial 5 is
parallelograms which it's built onto
由...提出
一架由
parallelograms which it's built onto
tutorial 15 is moving arms and tutorial
不对称v形折叠，所以我现在运行
通过一些角度等距
tutorial 15 is moving arms and tutorial
24 is circular movement so those are all
甚至看几个例子
这个小角度是30度
24 is circular movement so those are all
used to make that that mechanism and the
这是90度，在页面上
脊柱和它之间的角度
used to make that that mechanism and the
other one I'd like to show you is this
坚持下来是30和角度
在脊椎之间还是粘在这里
other one I'd like to show you is this
one very different
整件事都是90时
整个单身生活和你一样
one very different
this is pop-up book and Nursery Rhymes
可以看到整个这样关闭
事情向前发展，所以你可以建立
this is pop-up book and Nursery Rhymes
again it's by Mathew Reinhardt this is
平行四边形到此襟翼上
这个版本的角度和基数是
again it's by Mathew Reinhardt this is
the spread so in this case this is the
还是30但小角度和
不对称v折为35，且角度为
the spread so in this case this is the
structure that's been raised on the one
底数是90，
不对称v折是95，所以我做了一个
structure that's been raised on the one
side of this crease here and the
这些是您所拥有的
在不对称上有大角度
side of this crease here and the
asymmetric V pod is actually hidden
件是95，它的小角度是
在40度的基础上，您有90度
asymmetric V pod is actually hidden
underneath this floating plane so here
35所以我会坚持那个乐队
可以看到所有这些情况
underneath this floating plane so here
you can see this is the floating plane
不对称，所以你有一个小角度
在弹出窗口超过了大角度
you can see this is the floating plane
this is the asymmetric V fold which has
页面上弹出的大角度
越过页面上的小角度，所以
this is the asymmetric V fold which has
been used to raise this structure if you
那样会粘住
我将其粘在上面
been used to raise this structure if you
look at this structure end on you can
我已经测量了底座上的位置
然后在弹出窗口中，我就可以完成所有操作
look at this structure end on you can
see it's all parallelograms all being
而不是坚持一侧，
让它找到自然的位置
see it's all parallelograms all being
raised by
坚持下去
在那里，它关闭了我
raised by
one plane which is lifted by the
将此襟翼留在顶部只是为了
可以在上面建立平行四边形
one plane which is lifted by the
asymmetric v-fold so now I'll just run
这真的是有用的提示
在基地的一侧建造东西
asymmetric v-fold so now I'll just run
through some angles for the isometric